Visit turkision.com for more!
Kill them!
Aim! Shoot!
Praise be.
-My Bey has escaped, thank Allah.
-Thank Allah.
However, not only my Osman
Bey. Holofira also escaped.
Alps, we will go to the meeting
point before soldiers arrive.
Catch them!
Son, stop standing around. Come, sit.
Didn't you say that Gonca is alright?
She is alright, however, only for now.
If his father and house keep
on feeding their anger like this..
-..how will my Gonca be alright?
-We will all be with you, brother.
-She will be alright.
-I hope so.
-Alaeddin!
-My Gonca.
My baby.
Our baby is alright.
Are you alright? You scared us.
Thank Allah.
My Allah, thank you. My father.
Is my father alright?
Mother, is my father alright?
He is alright, my daughter.
However, he hasn't woke up yet.
You will look after yourself from now on, Hatun.
You will be careful for
both yourself and our baby.
No tiring yourself and getting upset.
How can I prevent it, Alaeddin.
Even if I prevent my tongue..
..I can not prevent my heart.
So, that is how children are.
When you become a mother and a father..
..you only live for your children.
Right.
How does my father hold on?
My father’s anger does not go away.
It is a hard burden to bear.
He is like this because he misses you.
He acts stubborn, however..
He does not give it up, does he?
-Are we allowed?
-Come in.
Sister.
Are you alright?
You scared me.
I am alright, brother.
-My father- -He is sleeping.
You be alright.
I wish none of this had happened.
But it did.
Anyways, you have some
rest. I'll check on my father.
Come on, have some rest.
Come on, my daughter.
Alaeddin.
If my brother softened up,
maybe my father will forgive me.
I hope so, my rose, my Gonca.
Then, after my father wakes up..
..I will tell him time of marriage.
After my father gets up, then
we will make marriage, right?
Of course we will.
-We did good with bows, valiants.
-Thank Allah.
Did you see how my Bey
smacked that dog down?
If that dog didn't have thick
armor, it would've ended there.
My Bey is coming!
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too, my Bey.
My Bey, thank Allah you are here.
-Are you alright?
-I am alright.
Thank Allah.
I hope our Allah who united us will
grant us victory as well.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
What will we do now, my Bey?
Are we heading back home?
No, we will not.
On the contrary, we will make
every land we step on our home.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
-So, my Bey..
You showed him well.
Yes.
Now, since we won't come
back, Konstantin will be on our tail.
He will hunt us.
We will show him who really is the hunter.
Until we have his head..
-..there is no going back.
-As you command, my Bey.
Now, Gocers and Yoruks.
We will stand by them.
We will make them settle. So that..
..Bursa and Iznik shall be the land of Turks.
If Allah permits.
Come on. Solgur Agha..
..must've had the tribe
settled. Let us go to him.
My Bey. You put yourself in danger for Holofira.
-May you prosper.
-Holofira is like my daughter.
Her heart is like of our Baciyans.
He put herself in danger for us.
And we won't hold back giving our life for her..
..when the time comes.
-Thank you, my Bey.
Now, she gained trust in Konstantin's eyes..
..by falling to the trap knowingly.
That is why, Tugay and Husrev
will get information from Holofira.
Come on alps, we are leaving.
I am ready to leave, my Shahzade,
however, you haven't told me where.
You will go to Bursa, Kanyumaz.
This here says that Holofira is Osman's spy.
You will give this to Commander Konstantin.
A spy?
They'll kill Holofira Hatun, my Shahzade.
And we'll be blamed for this.
-They'll know what I want them to know.
-How?
I wrote...
...the letter in the name of a
woman who hates Holofira.
Elcim Hatun.
Yes, Elcim.
I didn't write her name in
the letter. But everybody...
...even Constantin will
think it was written by Elcim.
Nobody will blame us, Kanyumaz.
We'll damage Osman and his family in this way.
Come on.
Deliver the letter as soon as possible.
Don't get yourself exposed.
As you order, my Shahzade.
-Peace be upon you!
-Peace be upon you too, Osman Bey!
Praise be. Praise be.
You've finished the half of the tribe together!
-My Bey, welcome to my tribe.
-Thank you.
Our soldiers are working without resting.
They wanted to stop to
welcome you, but I didn't let.
I wanted to prepare our tribe first.
Thank you.
Duty comes first.
Thank you, Solgur Agha. Well...
We'll work without rest so
we will lose as least as we can.
-Welcome, my Bey.
Thank you, thank you.
-May your work be easy! Praise be!
-Thank you!
-Thank you.
-Aameen.
-Well...
-My Bey.
I'll get the fattest goat in
my tribe slaughtered for you.
Great Solgur Agha will get only one slaughtered?
I will get ten goats slaughtered!
Hey, calm down. Don't slaughter animals in vain.
Well, my Bey... Osman Bey has
ebme to my tribe with his warriors.
Not ten.
Twenty goats!
Well, I'll go pick mine then.
I can pick the best from
the baa sound, you know.
Come here!
A guest should eat what
he's offered, Cerkutay Bey.
Nothing can run away from
my brother, my Shahzade.
Well, Solgur Agha... One
for the alps, one for Cerkutay.
As you order, my Bey.
Yes! I got one!
Alaeddin, tell me.
Is my father alright? Don't
hide anything from me.
Be patient, Mehmed.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Come on, Yakup Bey.
Wake up already. Come on.
Son, how is he doing?
His breath is good, mother.
-He'll regain strength as he rests, I hope.
-I hope so.
-Father.
-My Gonca.
Father?
Why did you leave the bed?
I just couldn't wait, Alaaddin.
-Let me sit with my father.
I promise I won't tire myself. -Fine.
Sister, Alaaddin is right.
-You should rest.
I'm fine, brother. I'll stay with father.
Well... Why is my father
still sleeping, Alaaddin?
Don't be afraid, dear. It's
because of healing herbs.
They'll help him have a
nice sleep and regain strength.
Yes.
My daughter... My daughter.
-My daughter.
-Father.
My daughter. Gonca...
Father.
I'm here, father.
I'm with you, father.
I'm here.
I'm here with you, father.
-Gonca.
-Father.
Father...
I miss you so much, father.
I miss you so much.
I miss you calling me daughter.
I miss you saying "my Gonca" to me, father.
Father... Father.
Please wake father.
Please wake up. Wake up, father.
Call me daughter again,
please. Open your eyes, father.
Wake up.
Have you forgiven me?
-Father, please.
-My daughter...
-My Gonca.
-Father.
Holofira...
My dear cousin..
You did a great job.
We found Osman on the road you said.
But we lost him, for now.
-That's not an issue for us.
Orhan is still in love with me.
He will come to Bursa again for me.
This time, we will not miss that
opportunity. I will rip the hearts of...
...Orhan and Osman.
I don't want you to go to the
monastery for some more time.
You will keep serving us.
If they are going to die in the end...
...I'd be happy to do it, Konstantin.
Have the Emperor's ships set sail, Commander?
The ships set sail, sir.
Our soldiers are ready to
enter the Yalikova harbour.
We will set out in the morning.
We will be on the road at dawn, Commander!
Holofira!
You proved that you are an
honourable member of Paleolugus family.
This i$an honor that will last me a lifetime.
Dastard... shameless...
Just like her father! She..
...betrayed us and
Byzantium. She deceived me.
Who sent us this unsigned letter?
A woman in pain..
...who is disturbed by
Orhan's past with Holofira.
A woman who is jealous of her.
Elcim Hatun.
Holofira heard what she needed to hear.
Osman.
...will fall into our trap tomorrow.
Andrea will follow Holofira.
I will keep using her until I get rid of Osman.
Until... the day that I will strangle her comes.
The taxes that we will send to the
Constantinople are ready, Commander Konstantin.
These golds are vital for the
army the Emperor will establish.
Take the golds out of the city
silently from beneath the walls.
Get lost!
Brothers! Brothers! What
are you doing without me?
You are cooking my goat.
My goat...
This is my goat!
This is my goat... -Brother...
A wolf took your goat, Cerkutay.
My... -Solgur Agha...
...had set aside the biggest one for you, but...
Yes...
Only a wolf and you have
that appetite, Cerkutay Bey...
A wolf took my big goat..
Brother... You see, your goat...
..fled towards the mountain.
My goat is gone.
What am I going to do now?
Now this is...
...your share, brother.
This?
What am I going to die?
I'm going to die of hunger.
What am I going to do?
I am going to die of sorrow.
What am I going to do, brothers?
Where should we put Cerkutay Bey's goat?
My brother!
My goat is here!
Now I will go and put my goat on the table...
There are people who are jealous of my goat!
It is halal to you, enjoy it.
Thank you, Solgur Agha.
Come on then.
Let's not keep our Bey waiting.
-May it heal, my Bey.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy, my Bey.
-Thank you, thank you.
Yoruks' fate is migrating again.
The tribes in the East are
now migrating to the west.
Tell me, Konur, how many
tribes have we established?
My Bey, there were a total of 24 tribes.
Ten of them, including this one,
have reached their destination.
The rest are still on the way.
They are on the way, but they are in danger.
Constantine will now be waiting
for an opportunity to attack them.
That's why we must always be ready.
Once again, we are at the
borders as we used to be.
We face the enemy hand-to-hand.
Whenever we face them hand-to-hand...
...we become stronger, my Bey. It
will be the same again, if Allah permits.
-If Allah permits.
My Bey, as long as that Constantine dog lives
we will always be dealing with this trouble.
They have sent soldiers
from Constantinople and Iznik.
Right, right.
But...
We will always be ready.
We will know every move they make.
We will always be after them, don't worry.
Come on then, everyone is hungry.
Cerkutay is also hungry, look at him.
-Isn't that right, Cerkutay? You're hungry.
-I am not, my Bey.
Alright then, let me tell you a long story.
What happened, Cerkutay?
Anyway, let's not give him a heart failure.
Come on, Cerkutay, start eating.
Enjoy your meals, Beys. You can eat now.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Cerkutay... Brother...
Eat a little slower you'll choke.
You should not be afraid of
men who eat, Boran brother!
You should not be afraid of men who eat,
you should be afraid of men who do not eat.
Men who do not eat are
sick. Men who do not eat...
...are weak.
Men who do not eat are low.
Brother... When are we going
to organize your wedding?
The weather has warmed up as well.
Right...
Fatma is right.
Once Yakup Bey recovers...
...and Osman Bey and Orhan return...
...we will organize your wedding.
We talked about that this morning.
Let's wait for Yakup Bey to recover...
We don't know if my
father is going to forgive us.
Let's organize your wedding!
I will defeat you in the competition
of carrying sheep, Shahzade!
You will see. -Do you hear him?
We know the winner of that competition, Ghazi.
Do not tire yourself.
-Is that what you think?
You had enough. I need strength!
I swear,
I will defeat you.
Come on then, eat.
How is Yakup Bey?
I believe he will be alright once he
recover, Elcim Hatun.
I hope so. If there is
something that I can do...
...Gonca...
-No, Elcim.
Gonca...
Forgive me for...
...what I said about your father.
I said all those things because of my anger.
I will go and take food to my brother. Enjoy.
She is worried about her father,
Elcim Hatun. Do not misunderstand her.
No, she is right. I made a mistake.
I kept saying bad words...
Then Yakup Bey got sick.
Those things might happen,
my daughter. We are a family.
We may fight and get offended...
...but we come together at
the same table and make peace.
Constantine is going to Yalikova.
He will set out in the morning.
Constantine will set out in the
morning. He will go to Yalikova.
I will go and inform Osman Bey now.
You will stay here and
keep doing your duty, Husrev.
My Bey...
If you accept... a dagger sheath.
I made it with my own hands, my Bey.
It is beautiful.
But... this is not just a sheath..
There are some little secrets on this, huh?
Alright, alright.
I hope you won't need it my Bey, but...
...I made it just in case you
might need it in the future.
Thank you.
I will carry it proudly.
-Thank you my Bey.
-Live long.
May it bring you blessings,
my Bey. Thank you, cerkutay.
I didn't want to say it, but...
How did you bring that
Constantine dog off his horse?
The man fell and rolled like a falling egg.
But he didn't crack. It
will also happen if Allah permits.
-If Allah permits.
But this move will make
Constantine even more angry, my Bey.
He was disgraced before his soldiers.
Orhan Bey is right.
Constantine is different than the others.
His mind works differently.
Thus, he will want to take his revenge.
Thanks for the blessings
my Allah granted us with...
Aameen. Thanks to Him.
Thanks to Him... Or else,
how would we feed this priest?
He was a talented priest,
my Bey. He showed the way...
..to heaven to that poor man.
My Bey... Don't, please.
They are already making fun of me.
They keep asking me "How are we
going to go to heaven, Priest Efendi?"
No, stop! Baysungur told me everything.
Right Baysungur? Come on!
Tell us, what did Cerkutay say?
Look for God on the ground. Go ahead.
Then you will find heaven.
Yes, you will. Look for God, son.
I didn't do like this, my
Bey. He's making up a story.
You felt at home in Bursa.
It was for the duty, my Bey.
What did you say?
Well... Well...
A man came to me.
And he asked how to go to heaven.
"Go straight. How can I know
everything? I said and he went away.
You told him the shortest way
Cerkutay. Praise be to you!
-Boran.
-My Bey.
I haven't listened to your kopuz for long.
-Do you have new lyrics?
-Sure, my Bey.
I composed one recently.
Play your kopuz. So...
...our lights will be cheered!
As my Bey orders.
A warrior comes forward to fight!
He is called Osman the Brunet!
Fighting for jihad!
Fine warriors stand with you.
Those harming the
innocent shall die soon.
The whole world shall
learn about the order, we will teach.
Heart shall burn!
The innocents shall find cure!
Arrows shall hit the target!
Mountains shall thunder!
Heart shall burn!
The innocents shall find cure.
Arrows shall hit the target!
Mountains shall thunder!
Once Bey of Beys wages war...
Once brave warriors let out a yell...
Kneel, the cruel!
Your heads will fall.
All the innocent shall rejoice!
Their screams shall be ended!
All the domes shall find freedom.
The whole world shall
learn about the order, we will teach.
Heart shall burn!
The inncocents shall find cure!
Arrows shall hit the target!
Mountains shall thunder!
Heart shall burn!
The inncocents shall find cure!
Arrows shall hit the target!
Mountains shall thunder!
Praise be! Well sung!
Thank you, my Bey! Long live you!
We'll reach every target with
and behind you, if Allah permits.
-If Allah permits.
Our target is The Red Apple.
With Allah's will, we'll reach it.
If Allah permist, my Bey.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
-If Allah permits.
What are you doing here?
Kanyumaz, what are you doing in Bursa?
Didn't Osman Bey forbid Germiyans?
Husrev, Osman’s leashed dog.
-Are you a spy now?
-I can become anything for my nation.
What about you?
You can only dig people's
graves for your own interests.
-Tell me. What are you doing here?
-What am I doing?
I will tell you but after
I take your filthy life!
You made a mistake by confronting me, Husrev.
Nobody should know I was here.
This way, come on!
Praise be!
Stir, Aykut! Stir!
This is a treasure. Marrow.
This can resurrect the dead!
And this here..
..is marrow soup!
Praise be.
A little thyme..
..a litle peppermint..
..and now it is delicious.
So you're saying we will be able
to climb walls after drinking this?
You will fly!
Tugay is coming. He wouldn't
have if it wasn't important.
We need to be cautious.
Aykut.
Cerkutay Bey, come on.
The soup. Let me!
-Let me take a spoon at least!
-Come on, Cerkutay Bey.
A spoonful!
-Just a spoonful Baysungur!
-Now it is all mine.
We are protecting the
routes from all sides, my Bey.
There are soldiers protecting the area ahead.
If an attack comes from one side,
they will let us now with a signal.
The others will then go to support.
Yoruks and alps are ready to ready.
You are talking about our moves.
What about what the enemy is doing?
Iznik and all castles are being
watched by our scout alps, my Bey.
We are ready at Bursa as well.
Then, tell Aykurt..
..to check all of our preparations.
-Thank you, my Bey.
-My Bey.
-What is it, Tugay?
We got information from Holofira, my Bey.
Konstantin is on his way to Yalakova.
There are support ships
coming from Constantinople.
Tell alps to be ready. You will come with us.
Alright, my Bey.
Konstantin. Yalakova will be your grave.
Wake up, father.
Open your eyes, father.
Tell me you forgive me.
Please, father.
Father, I am very tired.
I didn't know this would
weigh this much to my heart.
Now I am having a baby.
I will be a mother.
Now I understand.
Father, I understand your pain now.
Please forgive me.
Forgive me.
Father.
-Gonca?
-Father, you woke up!
You woke up!
My father! Brother!
-Father has awoken!
-Father.
-Father!
My father!
-I am alright.
-So you healed, father.
-Mehmed, where am I?
-At Osman's tribe.
What am I doing in here?
What am I doing in here Mehmed?
You got sick, father.
My brother brought you here.
Alaeddin healed you.
Father.
Father, I know.
It is a burden to your heart
as much as it is to mine.
Forgive me.
Let this late morning end.
I haven't did my wedding yet.
I waited for you to heal.
Allah is my witness, I did.
-Father.
Good news coming from you can not be good.
You waited you say.
Since you loved your father that much..
..where was your mind?
Gonca is not to blame,
father. It was all because of me.
I had no other choice but to bring you here.
Gonca is not alright, father.
She almost lost her baby because
of how upset she got about you.
-Father.
Take me to the marketplace.
I will make h...
Father, don't be stubborn, sit down.
Father, please. You have to rest.
Alaeddin told us to wait.
Being in debt..
..is making me weaker.
Mehmed. Make your preparations.
-We are leaving here tomorrow.
-As you command, father.
My Bey. Konstantin's soldiers are coming.
Come on then. It is time to
have Gunduz Bey's revenge.
It is a trap, he is not Konstentin.
It seems they knew we were
coming. Someone snitched.
-They blocked the road, my Bey.
-Since there is no way..
..then we will make one.
Today, you die, Osman.
You were saying the field of truth.
I brought you the truth.
-You will die.
-Truth lies at the end of my blade!
And it knows who to kill well.
Alps, they are many. This will be tough.
Take formations!
Alps! Stand still, we will get out!
Hold on!
-Protect Osman Bey!
-Shut it, Boran!
I haven't died yet!
-Allah is the greatest!
In the name of the cause!
Allah is the greatest!
Mercy has caused trouble, Aleksios.
We should have killed you in the tribe.
Don't you wonder how you
fell into the trap today, Orhan?
It was a letter from the tribe
that told us about your plan.
Someone who knows the great love
between you and Holofira and envies.
Who can it be Orhan?
-Don't you have a guess, Orhan?
-Shut up!
You inglorious dastard, come here.
Osman Bey isn't on his own! Attack!
It's time to fight for Osman Bey! Strike, alps!
Osman!
I'll be back!
Constantin... Where are you going?
I couldn't take even one spoon
from the soup because of you!
Killing even a thousand of you won't satisfy me!
You will never stop doing vile things, right?
Come here, dastards!
One way or another I'll bury
you in this forest, Constantin.
Come, Osman.
We'll see whose grave this place is.
Attack!
My Bey! My Bey! Where is Osman Bey, alps?
Where is our Bey, Boran?
He must have gone after that dog, brother.
We should go catch up! Come on!
Come here!
-Where did those dastards come from?
-They want to stop us.
Alps, our Bey is in danger.
We should break through them quickly!
-Here we go. Allah is the greatest!
-Allah is the greatest!
Welcome to your death Osman!
Everybody will talk about my victory.
Magnificent
Constantin Paleologus...
...slaughtered Osman, the cruel
leader of Osman, with his bare hands!
In the end, you will be on the ground.
-And I will keep standing.
-We don't...
...fight to be remembered.
Many anonymous warriors
sacrificed their blood for these lands.
Neither you nor me..
What matters is who will keep standing.
Byzantine or the glorious state of Turks!
Ancient Rome will always prevail in these lands.
But you won't live long
enough to see those days.
Archers!
You turn the field of bravery into
the field of vileness again, huh?
Bravery... Vileness... These
are just empty words, Osman.
Only the winning write history.
You say so?
We'll follow the river to the end!
I'll make sure he's dead! Let's go!
Baysungur.
-My Shahzade...
Go to the tribe now.
Holofira's life is in danger.
That dog named Alexios said that...
...a Hatun from our tribe
informed them about Holofira.
Is this why we fell into their trap
my Shahzade? But who did this?
According to what that dog said...
...Elcim Hatun did this.
My Shahzade, how did this happen?
-Go to the tribe now.
My Bala mother do what
is necessary. Go now.
Yes my Shahzade.
My Shahzade. Did something bad happen?
What did Alexius tell you?
-That dog was just barking, Konur Bey.
It's not important. Alps! We
will go after my father. Come on!
The river must've swallowed Osman’s
dead body already. Check everywhere!
Commander Constantine..
Osman's Alps are looking for him.
We cannot stay here. Let's go back.
Besides, you are injured.
Sooner or later, we wjll find them.
I want Osman's dead body, Alexios!
No one will leave until we find him!
We will find Osman dead or alive.
But... if his Alps come here
this might not be possible.
Besides... there are just a few of us and you
are injured. Doctors must treat your wound.
Osman! Neither your dead body...
...nor your living body will escape from me!
No one will return to the
city until you find Osman!
We will spend the night at
the headquarters in Saklivadi.
When will my father come back,
mother? We still haven't heard from him.
How can we ask a man who went to
fulfill his duty when he will come back?
Sisters!
Give that to me.
So... Draw your sword. Show me your talent.
Alright... So you want to test me, huh?
Let's see if your wrist
got stronger, Fatma sister.
Come on.
-Praise be to my daughter.
-I am your student.
We will see.
Osman... -Mother..
Mother... Mother... Are you
alright? Mother, forgive me!
My Allah... Protect my Osman and my Orhan...
Let us be victorious in this war.
Mother... mother... mother, are you alright?
My daughter...
Mother, forgive me.
-My daughter, I am alright. Don't be afraid.
I am alright. I am alright.
It's not your fault. I am alright.
For a moment I felt bad.
I am now alright.
-Mother...
Don't be afraid... Don't
be afraid... I am alright.
Mother... I was so afraid.
-I am alright.
-There's still no trace of my father!
-We will find him, Orhan Bey.
We will find him.
Osman Bey was here. The
dead bodies of the dogs are here.
Contantine dog... He is luring
my father into a trap again.
They must be around!
Alps! Everyone will be on alert!
We will find my father.
We will find him. Come on!
The Sultan of words..
Iltutan...
Once again, a great battle
has fallen to your share.
What are you doing here?
The ground and the sky belong to Allah.
There's nothing else but Him.
We are living our lives
with what He gives to us.
I'm making soup...
...for you. What are you doing here?
There... I fell into the trap of the infidels.
As you can see... I am now here.
You did not fall into a trap.
The trap appeared in the middle of the
way when you were approaching your target.
How can you reach your
target before getting over it?
Then...
...do I still have a long way to go?
You still have a long way to go.
There is You within you.
First, the curtain will be raised.
Then like Hadhrat Abraham, your path is clear.
You have your sword in
your hand to remove the idols.
The One Who...
...created me will surely show me the way.
May your horse be your companion
may Mount Kesis be your guide...
...may Allah help you.
Yunus Emre..
Yunus Emre!
Yunus Emre.. Yunus Emre! Yunus Emre!
Where are you, Dervish?
If you hadn't found me...
...I wouldn't have been
able to find my way.
Now if I cannot walk on
this path, I will be disgraced.
Iltutan...
You are showing me the way again.
It's as if the ground swallowed
them! Where are they?
Cerkutay Bey! It's your
turn now! Find their tracks!
Alps! Keep looking around! Come on!
Are you still thinking about what
Alexius dog said, my Shahzade?
Right... Holofira is in danger.
No, my Shahzade. Elcim Hatun would not do that.
What do you think, my Shahzade?
-I also don't want to believe it, Konur Bey.
Those dogs might be playing
a game, but Elcim Hatun...
I know Elcim Hatun's attitude towards Holofira.
May Allah forbid, what if that
dog does something to Holofira?
We will find Osman Bey first! We will find him.
There are too many tracks!
What are we going to do now?
-This is dog Constantine.
He did this to stop us from following him.
Karesi Bey. Let's scatter and search
for Osman Bey. Let's not waste any time.
Sure. Let's just find our Osman Bey...
...safe and sound.
-Yes, Karesi Bey.
You go south I'll go west.
May Allah help us. Come on!
-Come on Alps!
I bear witness that there is none
worthy of worship except Allah...
...and I bear witness that Muhammad(PBUH)
is His servant and Messenger.
They want to ruin us.
Thanks to Allah, we can't go
back from this path anymore.
No going back. There is no god but Allah.
There is no god but Allah.
Osman's horse! This way, come on!
Footprints all around! There was a fight here!
Also blood trails on the ground.
This is dog Constantin's doing!
Obviously, they drew my Bey into an ambush.
An arrow of heathens! It
seems my Bey broke it off.
Where are you my Bey?
My Bey's dagger. He was here!
No. No way.
Not at all, brother,
No daggers can fall off the sheath Aykut made.
Osman Bey would never
leave his dagger behind. Is he...
Tugay!
Don't... Say no more.
We'll find our B£y. We'll leave
no stones unturned and find him!
Sir, you're bleeding. We should stop it.
I want reinforcement forces in
Bursa right here immediately, Aleksios.
I've sent a message. They'll be here soon, sir.
Place the soldiers around the headquarters.
Send four men to the river
and tell them to hide well.
Let's see if they can find the alps and Osman.
Soon..
I will...
...get rid of Osman for good.
Mother, are you alright?
I'm fine. I just don't feel comfortable.
-I'll go take fresh air.
-Mother, are you alright?
Brother, this is the second time. It
also happened during the training.
Are you sick, mother? Brother?
Did you exhaust yourself, mother?
-I can examine you.
-No, son. I'm not exhausted.
I just have a bad feeling.
I feel it at times. But it's alright.
I'll go refresh my ablution.
-Come on.
-Do I have permission, Bala Hatun?
Come in!
Baysungur. Good or bad news?
I've brought a message from Shahzade Orhan.
The dog called Constantin...
..drew us into an ambush.
Orhan?
What are you saying Baysungur?
Are Osman Bey and Orhan alright?
Orhan sent the message. And Osman?
We don't know where Osman Bey is.
What do you mean? What
are you saying, Baysungur?
Weren't you with him?
And my brother? Where is he?
Shahzade Orhan...
...is looking for Osman Bey with the alps.
-We got separated from Osman Bey.
-My Allah...
Protect my father, my Allah.
Tell me, Baysungur. How could
Osman Bey fall into the ambush?
They found out that Holofira was a spy.
They drew Osman Bey into the ambush.
If Holofira is exposed, it
means there is a traitor.
Baysungur.
-There is more.
-A hatun in the tribe...
..sent a letter to Aleksios.
-Who said that? -Shahzade Orhan heard himself.
He heard what?
Aleksios got the letter...
What letter? Tell me who
sent the letter, Baysungur.
Aleksios...
He implied Elcim Hatun.
What?
Are you hearing yourself,
Baysungur? What are you talking about?
-Elcim.
-Bala Hatun.
My Shahzade Orhan told me to tell you..
..that you would know what to do.
So you finally woke up. Thank God.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy.
Are you alright?
Thanks to you, I am alright.
What about you?
Why are you helping a Turk?
We saved a wounded man.
We didn't ask who you were.
However, do you allow us to ask about your name?
My name
-..is Mustafa.
-So you are carrying the name of our Prophet.
-So you know Him. -More than that..
..Yunus Emre told us many times.
Mushroom soup, drink it.
The only friend of us monks out in the forest.
It will make you stronger.
We've collected mushrooms and made soup..
..so that you can drink it.
May your horse be your friend
Monk Mountain your map..
..and Allah be your guide.
What about your name, monk?
I am Simon. You were in
rough shape when we found you.
God has protected you.
Aren't you going to ask?
Who put me in this shape?
Who will you face against?
We do not ask what.
The One who put you in our
way must've thought about it.
Now, you are wondering what are we doing here.
Yes. What are you doing in here?
Empire's religion does not accept us.
However, our hearts do not
accept their religion as well.
Alright, good. Do not worry..
..you surely have a home as well.
Alaeddin, send Baysungur
and Orhan alps for support.
-No, let me go as well, mother.
-You will stay here, son.
The tribe is entrusted to you. Come on.
Come on Baysungur.
Do you not believe me? Bala Hatun?
Gonca.
-Fatma, you too?
-I..
..do not know who is guilty. I
am thinking about my father.
I got married for the good of this tribe.
Would I disrupt this union
with my own hands now?
You didn't want Orhan to
go to Bursa, right, Elcim?
Yes. I did not want to.
I did not want him to see Holofira.
Elcim, if you did this with a sudden anger..
..we understand you. Tell us the truth.
I do not mix my personal emotions
with State affairs, I did not do it!
No one else knew Holofira was a spy.
Don't do this, Bala Hatun.
Ulgen, Kismet.
Elcim will not leave her tent..
..until Osman Bey and Orhan comes.
She will see no one. Put alps on her door.
Elcim is not someone who
can make such a huge mistake.
Of course not. However she is a human as well.
Longing can make one blind, my daughter.
We will reveal the truth with justice.
We did wrong for years, Kanyumaz.
We thought we would've
defeated Osman with swords.
However, look what a letter did.
They are now against themselves.
Mind is greater than sword, my Shahzade.
So Osman hid Husrev at Bursa as a spy.
What good can that do, my
Shahzade. He is dead now.
I took his life myself.
Alright. We will break Kayis like this.
Look, now they have chaors in the tribe.
-What tribe are you talking about, Mehmed?
-Father.
What is happening in the tribe?
Osman.
..went to attack Konstantin, however..
..he fell to a trap.
They say Elcim Hatun told Konstantin..
..about Osman's attack.
Elcim Hatun you say.
Nevermind, father.
You get some rest.
Let them eat each other.
According to our belief..
..every human God has created
is equal to one and another.
Rich and poor are the
same in the face of justice.
Just like in divine religions.
Of course, whoever has the power..
..does not allow it.
-Unfortunately.
Those who hold that power..
..are the ones who banished us.
We couldn't settle in neither Iznik nor Bursa.
Monk Mountain became our home.
Iznik was..
..the land of Turks at Suleyman Shah's era.
Did issues like this happened back then?
Nikea is one of the holiest..
..cities of the
World of Christianity.
Maybe the most holiest, after Quds.
While it was at the hands of Seljuks..
..the monks who escaped from
Byzantine used to take shelter in Iznik.
Still, Turks showed hospitality to us.
Until crusaders came.
You went against he Church
of the Emperor as well.
Didn't that make your situation harder?
We only walk on the path we know, Mustafa.
They bring the God to the human level.
They make Him an idol, material.
They put the cross on their armor..
..and commit murders..
..with fancy idols.
We believe that God is only one.
And he is always with us.
You are against this like us, muslims.
Do not worry. From now on..
..tyranny of oppressors won't continue.
Bursa and Iznik..
..will be the land of Turks sooner or later.
And you will live there forever.
In the name of Allah.
My Gonca, what are you doing here?
Didn't I tell you to rest?
Well, Alaaddin... I couldn't stay in
the tent thinking about my father.
Any news from Osman Bey?
-Gonca Hatun! Gonca Hatun!
-Hey! What are you doing?
-Mother, stop chasing me!
-Stop, Ghazi!
What are you doing, Ghazi?
-What is this?
-Your baby's gift, Gonca Hatun.
Is this your crib? Why are
you giving her this old thing?
-Mother, don't touch! Don't touch!
-Ghazi!
I'm a grown up man!
You won't have another baby, anyway.
-And this isn't my crib.
-Do whatever you want.
Another baby? I can hardly control
you. Another one? No, thanks.
Ghazi.
You didn't do what I think, did you?
Look at me.
What are you talking about?
This is for your baby, Gonca Hatun.
Where did you find this, Ghazi? Ha, boy?
Someone made it and put it outside.
And I just took it. Huh, Gonca Hatun?
-How do you like it?
-Very nice.
You did well boy...
You made it?
I was going to bring it
when it was finished, but...
...Ghazi did Ghazi things again.
It's beautiful.
I gave you the gift but you're hugging Shahzade.
-Come here, I'll show you how to hug!
-Alaaddin!
-This is a test from Allah, right?
-Don't you say, Ulgen!
I'm sorry.
He makes us smile even in these hard times.
-My Hatun.
-Yes.
Yakup Bey and Mehmed Bey are leaving.
Let's go see your father off, my dear.
Alps, take this to the tent.
My Allah.
You know me better than I myself do.
They're attempting to play tricks...
...and drive a wedge between me and my family.
Don't let them, my Allah.
Lead their tricks..
...to their deaths. Aameen.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Bala Hatun, we want to see Elcim Hatun.
Elcim Hatun is innocent!
We want to see Elcim Hatun.
Bala Hatun, we want to see Elcim Hatun.
What are you doing, Beys?
Gunduz Bey trusted us to look after her.
Since when have you been entering
Osman Bey's tent without permission?
We want to see Elcim Hatun.
We won't let her be slandered.
Who are you protecting her from?
From those who betray our trust!
Haydar Bey, my patience has limits.
If you go further, I won't
mind Gunduz Bey's memory.
You already dishonored his memory, Bala Hatun.
Enough! Put your swords down!
All of you!
Haydar Bey, this is not a matter
which can be discussed in public.
Hasan, take Beys to Osman Bey's tent.
-And host their alps in the tribe.
-As you order, Bala Hatun.
Haydar Bey, give me your swords.
Yakup Bey.
You should take these regularly.
For your health, you
have to. Don't be obstinate.
I owe you one, Alaaddin Bey.
You owe me nothing, Yakup Bey.
I did everything for my wife's sake.
Stay safe.
Sorry for the trouble.
Not at all.
Take a good care of your father, Mehmed.
He should take medicine on time.
I can take care of my father,
Alaaddin. Don't be worrying.
In fact, you should take care of your father.
Well... They say there's a traitor among you.
Ha, Alaaddin? There are many traitors among you.
You can't clear off those traitors.
That's why you never get rid of troubles.
Come on, Mehmed!
When my father sman Bey is back,
we will have the wedding, Yakup Bey.
We'd like to see you here with us.
I have no place in that wedding.
Enjoy your wedding.
Oh, Yakup Bey...
Come on, my dear.
Come on.
-Someone's coming.
-Hurry up! Hurry up!
Traitors.
Traitors..
-Leave the monks alone.
-This land belongs to the empire.
-It will be as we want.
-They harm nobody.
Show them mercy so you
will be treated in the same way.
Mercy should only be given to
those who deserve. These are traitors.
-Are you looking for someone?
-Osman.
That's why I told you to leave them alone.
The one who you're looking for is here.
-He's Osman.
-Yes, Osman.
This wounded wolf can even beat five of you.
Attack!
Now tell me where Constantin is.
Where is Constantin?
Come on! Search! Search!
Aleksios, you'll bring
Osman dead or alive to me!
Come on!
Nobody is going anywhere until you find Osman!
Find Osman for me!
Sir, you have a wound.
You shouldn't have come here.
Commander Constantin,
there are some trails here.
The soil is worn. Someone
crawled out of the stream.
He was bleeding.
He stitched his wound with horsehair.
That Osman did not die!
There are other footprints as
well. Someone took him away!
The footprints are going this way!
We will find Osman and
finish what we left half-finished.
Come on!
Tell me where he is, so
you will die right away.
In Saklivadi...
..at Kizilcinar.
Even if you don't know my
name, infidels will not forget it.
You hosted Osman Bey in your house. Thank you.
Nothing changed for us, Osman Bey.
You are bleeding.
-Thank you. Thank you.
We cannot stay here now. We have to go.
Right... From now on, you won't stay here.
Take this.
If you give this to someone...
...in my land, in my homeland...
..all doors will open for you.
You're giving us the key that will
open the doors of your land. Thank you.
Thank you.
And the key that will..
...open the doors of Bursa and Nikea...
...is the mercy in your heart.
Thank you.
Here, Osman Bey.
We washed and cleaned them.
Thank you, thank you.
Come on.
I heard from Alps. You are keeping
Elcim Hatun in her tent like a prisoner.
How did this happen?
We are doing
all these things...
...to secure justice, Haydar Bey.
What do you accuse Elcim Hatun of? Tell us.
It's a private matter that
shouldn't be discussed.
We will solve it within the family.
Don't you trust someone from your own family?
If you do not release Elcim Hatun now...
...both unity and order will be disrupted.
We won't remain silent about this.
-Stop there...
..Haydar Bey! Stop there!
Don't cross the line. It's not your place...
...to threaten us. Know your place.
It's not a threat it's the truth.
You are keeping Gunduz Bey's trust imprisoned.
How can we protect the unity now?
Beys! -We can.
Haydar Bey. And you will
wait calmly in your tribe.
The secret of the Kayi has been
revealed. We will find who did this.
Besides, Elcim is not just...
...Gunduz Bey's trust, she is
also a daughter of this family.
I won't sacrifice my daughter
in law to the slander of infidels!
Alaeddin!
Beys. We are doing what
is necessary for justice.
There's no need to worry.
Instead of wasting your
time with these matters...
...go and train your Alps.
There are many fortresses for Kayi to take.
You heard our daughter Elcim, Haydar Bey.
Go now, our Alps will accompany
you back to your tribe. Come on.
There's still no news from my
father or my brother/ mother.
There is no need to worry, my son.
Osman Bey is alright. I know that.
Come on. Everyone back to their duties!
Elcim..
Go to your tent now. I'll talk to you.
Where is this place?
-It must be the place of monks.
So they saved Osman.
Commander... Soldiers!
Osman.
So he was stron enough to kill the soldie
You will find the track of...
...Osman and the monks, Alexius.
I swear to Jesus..
I will send them to hell with my own hands.
Who are you? -Stop, Solgur Agha.
They are monks.
No one knows this forest better than you.
We are looking for our Bey. His name is Osman.
He is a brave Turk Bey. Tell me.
Have you seen him before?
Are you looking for the owner of this ring?
My Bey's ring.
Tell me now! Tell me!
How did you get this ring, huh?
Osman Bey gave it to us.
He said this ring would open
every door in his homeland.
Cut it short! Where is Osman Bey?
He was injured... We treated him.
Alps... Don't hurt them.
Where is he now?
Where did he go?
He went to keep his promise.
That's what he said to us.
-My Bey...
My Bey will go after Constantine.
Osman Bey is going to death alone.
It's obvious... There will be a fight.
But they will be the ones who die.
Alps... My Bey is injured. Come on!
I see disappointment in your
eyes, but I don't see regret, Elcim.
I haven't done anything to regret, Bala Hatun.
You know what happens if Holofira's
espionage is exposed, don't you?
Especially when Osman
Bey and Orhan were in Bursa...
...this means their lives were at risk.
-Yes.
Not only Holofira's life...
...but also Osman Bey's,
Orhan's, and the Alps' lives.
Only a stupid woman...
...who has become the servant of her weakness...
...blinded by jealousy
could reveal this secret...
-Or..
-Or?
I do not do such stupidity.
Or someone who is an enemy of Kayi.
This is treachery.
I do not betray my house, Bala Hatun.
I know.
You sacrificed many
things for this tribe, Elcim.
Then why are you keeping me in my tent?
Don't you trust my word?
The position I am in taught
me to never trust anyone.
We are humans.
We have weaknesses.
Everyone can make mistakes.
This slander brought upon me is no mistake.
This is not about Holofira as well.
Yes, I was jealous.
-Like every woman would do.
-However..
..this is a State issue.
And I have married for this State.
I do not put the future of The State in danger..
..for my own ambition.
I am not mad at you.
No matter what you do..
..you think about your Bey,
your children and your tribe.
However, I wonder one thing.
Do you believe me, Bala Hatun?
Were you looking for me? You snake! Traitor!
Do you serve Konstantin now after my aunt?
I do not forget anything.
Did you hear me? Never!
You will pay for everything.
However, first, you will tell me everything.
Did you hear me? Everything!
-I heard you.
-Everything!
Since Osman gathered his
strength and killed our soldiers..
..he must have gone to his tribe.
-No.
-He did not.
-However..
He will not leave before
finishing what he has started.
So am I.
I will find every tribe of his..
..and destroy each and every one of them.
He will come after me.
I am not a man who will cover behind..
..the walls of Constantinople.
Do not forget, Holofira does
not still know about the truth.
You Elcim Hatun sent a letter..
..to Konstantin. Is that so?
She told everything. You being Osman Bey's spy..
..why you are here and all that.
Do not lie to me.
Elcim wouldn't have done such a thing.
Why didn't Konstantin kill me yet? Tell me.
To use you until the end.
So you got into my way and
became my map, Gokboru.
Now, both conquest..
..and victory awaits us.
Visit turkision.com for more!